socialix.com 2018-09-04

# Privacy Policy - Privacy & Terms from Socialix

Last updated as of June 18, 2018.

Prana Interactive Inc. d/b/a Socialix and its affiliates, successors and assigns (“Socialix” or “Company” or we” or “us”) is the owner and operator of the website available at https://socialix.com/ (“Website”).

Your privacy is important to us, so we created this Privacy Policy to explain how your information is collected, used, stored and protected. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time and you can always review the most current version here. By using our Website, you consent to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and are aware that our policies may evolve in the future.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the privacy practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, services, and applications that you may access through Socialix. For example, Socialix utilizes the YouTube API as a third party, and you are agreeing to be bound by the YouTube Terms of Service (<https://www.youtube.com/t/terms>) and Privacy Policy (<http://www.google.com/policies/privacy>) when engaging YouTube content and services through Socialix.

**Protecting Your Privacy**

In various places on the Sites, we collect "Personally Identifiable Information", such as your name & e-mail address that can be used to identify you or contact you.Socialix will not share any of your Personally Identifiable Information, except for the information that you choose to publicly disclose with our advertisers or any third-parties for marketing purposes. Account information is password protected. Keep your password safe.

**Data We Collect**

In addition to Personally Identifiable Information you provide at registration or by using a third party API, we may collect the following information: Gender, age, location, interests, likes, and other information that you may decide to provide us with, or that you decide to include in your public profile. If you connect a web analytics service to the Socialix platform, we will also collect basic website or blog metrics, including but not limited your blogs number of monthly visitors and pageviews.

**How We Use Your Data**

Socialix collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve its site and services. These uses may include providing you with more effective customer service; making the site or services easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies; and displaying content customized to your interests and preferences. Socialix collects and uses your web analytics data is used to better serve clients and to promote your blog to advertising partners.

The information that you provide in your public profile will be made visible to advertisers, as well as your number of monthly blog visitors, should you connect your web analytics. You can delete your personal information or disconnect your web analytics at anytime.

**Data Storage and Security**

The following information is stored in our database, even after deletion, and may be archived: Registration information, server log files, historical web analytics data and other records.

Socialix uses commercially reasonable efforts to protect your personal information, including safeguards such as firewalls, password-protected databases with limited physical or electronic access, and encryption. In addition, Socialix may utilize secure technology such as SSL to transfer information provided by users, and additional measures in the processing of sensitive information. While we have taken efforts to guard your personal information, we cannot guarantee that your information may be not be disclosed or accessed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others. Your account information and access to certain portions of the Site is accessible only through the use of a user ID and password. To protect the confidentiality of personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of our Site and associated services by any person using your user ID and password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your user ID and password have been misused.to ensure that it is not made available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security.

**Disclosure of information**

Socialix may disclose information about its users if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: Respond to a legal process (e.g., subpoenas, court orders). Protect the rights, property or personal safety of Socialix, its users or the general public.

If Socialix is merged with or acquired by another company, the resulting combined company will use the information you have provided as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Questions**

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our use of your information, please contact us at contact@socialix.com.

Effective Date: April 1st  2015
